- 好的 那么... - 菲尔 听我说
- All right, so... - Phil, hear me out on this.
如果你是想说带着他一起 我同意
If it's about bringing him along with us, then yes.
好极了 瓦莱特 过来
Great. Wallet, get over here, buddy.
瓦莱特 你以前见过手机吗
Hey, Wallet, you ever see a phone before?
他喜欢手机
He likes that.
天啊 他牵着你的手
My God. He is holding your hand.
只是本能而已
Just intrinsically.
他就是看着手机然后伸手了
He's just looking at his phone and he reached up.
他抓着你的小指头
He's holding your pinky.
这不是我所期待的欢迎方式啊
Not quite the welcome I was expecting.
以为他们会有个
Thought they'd have like a branded step-and-repeat
品牌标志背景墙什么的
or something.
会有人来迎接我们对吧
Someone's gotta come welcome us, right?
他们说会有人来
They said there'd be someone.